leantesting.com 2016-05-28

# Privacy policy | Lean Testing

Lean Testing is developed and operated by Crowdsourced Testing SpA (the "Company".)

Your accessing of this website indicates your understanding, agreement to and acceptance, of the full privacy policy contained herein.

### Collection and use of personal information

Your data is used for purposes that you expect it to be used, namely providing services you requested.

This may include providing you personalized content, features to enable you to interact with others, securing your data, and communicating about, improving, or troubleshooting the products or services being provided.

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

As is true of most websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to:

  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Marketing Communications

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included at the bottom of these emails.

### Disclosure to third parties

Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of the Company.

We may disclose your personal information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Lean Testing to recognize you each time you visit this site.

Lean Testing uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Cookies are also used by a 3rd party provider, Google Analytics.

We use Google Analytics to gather information about how you and others use our website. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.

### Notification of privacy policy change

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective.

We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### External sites

Lean Testing is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

### Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**Crowdsourced Testing SpA**  
Bombero Nuñez 131  
Santiago, Region Metropolitana
